worldenglishinstitute.org 2013-07-17

# World English Institute - Free English Lessons

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which World English Institute collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.worldenglishinstitute.org website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by World English Institute.

### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information

World English Institute collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * _To personalize user experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * _To improve our Site_ We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To improve customer service_ Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * _To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature_ To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * _To send periodic emails_ The email address Users provide will only be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

### Changes to this privacy policy

World English Institute has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://www.worldenglishinstitute.org/privacy). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
World English Institute  
www.worldenglishinstitute.org  
World English Institute 1525 NW Division Gresham, OR 97030  
help@worldenglishinstitute.org  

This document was last updated on October 23, 2011.
